Wise Man Racine, under the check and conduct of the Holy Spirit, ministers prayer to Mrs Argiro Sakka.
Immediately, she falls to the ground under the healing influence of the Holy Spirit.
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
You can see her shaking against her will
as Jesus Christ is at work repairing and restoring her womb.
Come out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Be free, in the name of Jesus Christ!
In Jesus' name!
In Jesus name!
A few months later, Mrs Argiro Sakka came back to The Scoan with her husband, all the way from Greece, to share her testimony. Let's listen to her!
Praise the Lord!
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Mrs Argiro Sakka, Greece.
I am 34 years old.
This is my husband.
My name is Argiro Sakka, I come from Greece. I am 34 years old. This is my husband.
During my pregnancy, I was bleeding and the water broke two years ago,
so the doctors had to totally remove my womb and my menstruation stopped.
During my pregnancy, I had an infection, so the doctors had to totally remove my womb.
These are my medical reports that show that my womb was removed.
I had no menstruation.
I lost all hope that my menstruation could come back.
June 11th, 2010 I came to The SCOAN and Wise Man Racine prayed for me
and on August 13th, 2010 I had my menstruation for the first time in one year.
I came here last year, and Wise Man Racine prayed for me. After a while my period came again.
Three months after I received prayer, I went to the hospital
for examinations and the first part of my womb started showing.
Since then, my womb continued growing gradually
and now it has been recreated completely.
Three months after I received the prayer, I went back to the hospital,
and the doctors saw that my womb started to be recreated.
After the operation, the womb was removed.
The doctor confirmed that the womb was removed.
Since the womb had been removed, no more menstruation.
There is no way that she would have menstruation.
Last year, she came here, after she had not had her menstruation for a long time
because the womb was removed.
She was prayed for.
After that prayer, the womb was returned spiritually - by operation.
Now, she went to see the doctor,
and the doctor said, "You see your menstruation. How come when there is no womb?"
Then the doctor tested her and was shocked,
"Ah, I removed the womb. How come the womb has come back?"
As for me, I don't think any miracle is better than that
because the womb was removed, and the doctor confirmed it. The report is there to confirm it.
The menstruation had ceased for many years because the womb was removed.
After she dreamt that the womb had returned, she went to the doctor.
The doctor did a lot of tests, and the womb was returned.
Now, look at her here with the medical report and everything.
What is your problem?
That was last year.
Today, the Lord promises to give us a birthday gift -
freedom from that thing that has been disturbing you.
We have a medical doctor here.
What can you say about the womb removal, sir.
I would say that it is actually impossible that when a womb is removed
for it to ever regenerate.
So, this is just an act of God to have a new womb come back.
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Dr Vincent Nwosa, Md - The Bahamas, USA
So you listened to what the doctor said. He said, the act of God.
He cannot say more than that because it is humanly impossible.
This can only happen by God.
Invisible President!
Tell your neighbour, "Invisible President!"
He is the President of the invisible world.
Whatever we are doing here, we know that it is only an extension.
All what we are saying now, our meeting here,
it has happened before we have it here.
Everything we are doing is an extension.
The bank is over there.
When a miracle happens here, it has happened over there.
Before it happens here, it has happened over there.
Before we shout hallelujah, they have shouted over there.
This testimony has been given over there before we give it here.
Tell your neighbour, "Invisible President!"
Last year, I came to The SCOAN and the wise man prayed for me.
After the prayer, I went for examination and
I saw that my womb had been completely recreated.
My menstruation came back
and the doctor said I would be able to have a child.
Last year I came here to The SCOAN in Lagos, Nigeria. Wise Man Racine prayed for me.
After the prayer I went back home, and we went to the hospital.
These are the new medical examinations
that show that my womb is totally recreated.
My menstruation has come back, and the doctor has told me that I am able to bear a child once more.
Listen to that! Do you see the word the doctor used - recreated?
He agrees that it grows.
It's like you have a sore, and the face of the sore is so deep.
Suddenly, it grows - body can grow.
You know I used to say to you that there are spare parts of your body in the store.
If anyone is harmed, if anyone is injured,
go to the store, take it and just fix it.
Everybody has extra!
Your health - extra health is in the store.
In case your head hits something, they will open the store, give you another one, and remove this one.
We have spare parts.
When an area of your car is damaged,
you go to the market to buy a new part.
They would fix and remove the damaged part. The same thing applies to all parts of your body.
On the last day, by the time many of us will stand there,
God would just open the store and say, "Look - everything of your body. Look at the spare parts!
Look at this one that was hurt!
Instead of calling on me to let me open the store and give it to you, now see yourself!"
It's a womb.
If they removed your womb, and God created you,
it can be regenerated, it can be recreated.
It can regrow.
This is exactly what happened to the sister. It grew back.
Thank you.
We have listened to the wonderful testimony from Mrs Argiro Sakka
with her husband. They came all the way from Greece.
Wow!
I am happy because it really touched your faith.
It really struck that spirit in you.
It happened!
Nothing is impossible with His power.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmamuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.